<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
	<job>
		<title><![CDATA[New Job]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Sales Hiring Systems]]></company>
		<date><![CDATA[17-07-16]]></date>
		<referencenumber><![CDATA[142]]></referencenumber>
		<url><![CDATA[http://saleshiringsystems.com/job/sapir-holon-6-new-job/]]></url>
		<country><![CDATA[Haifa, Israel]]></country>
		<description><![CDATA[אנשי מכירות מוצלחים?
בעלי ניסיון של 2-3 שנים בתחום?
רוצים עבודה בחברה עם חברים לצוות ולחיים?

הגעתם למקום הנכון!
שלחו לנו קורות חיים ונחזור אליכם.]]></description>
		<jobtype><![CDATA[Internship]]></jobtype>
	</job>
	<job>
		<title><![CDATA[new]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Kajamba]]></company>
		<date><![CDATA[17-07-18]]></date>
		<referencenumber><![CDATA[143]]></referencenumber>
		<url><![CDATA[http://saleshiringsystems.com/job/sapir-2-new/]]></url>
		<country><![CDATA[Modi'in-Maccabim-Re'ut, Israel]]></country>
		<description><![CDATA[נפתחה משרה חדשה בתחום!
.פרטים יימסרו למתאימים לאחר שליחת קורות החיים]]></description>
		<jobtype><![CDATA[Part Time]]></jobtype>
	</job>
	<job>
		<title><![CDATA[Sales Manager]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Sales Hiring Systems]]></company>
		<date><![CDATA[17-07-20]]></date>
		<referencenumber><![CDATA[147]]></referencenumber>
		<url><![CDATA[http://saleshiringsystems.com/job/sales-hiring-systems-%d7%aa%d7%9c-%d7%90%d7%91%d7%99%d7%91-%d7%99%d7%a4%d7%95-%d7%9e%d7%97%d7%95%d7%96-%d7%aa%d7%9c-%d7%90%d7%91%d7%99%d7%91-4-sales-manager/]]></url>
		<country><![CDATA[Tel Aviv-Yafo, Israel]]></country>
		<description><![CDATA[משרה זמנית חדשה נפתחה!

רוצים להרוויח הרבה כסף בזמן קצר?!?

בואו הצטרפו לחברה הכי שווה שיש!

שלחו קורות חיים ונחזור אליכם בהקדם.]]></description>
		<jobtype><![CDATA[Temporary]]></jobtype>
	</job>
	<job>
		<title><![CDATA[Sales Manager]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[Varint]]></company>
		<date><![CDATA[17-07-15]]></date>
		<referencenumber><![CDATA[164]]></referencenumber>
		<url><![CDATA[http://saleshiringsystems.com/job/ahs-3-sales-manager/]]></url>
		<country><![CDATA[Ramat Gan, Israel]]></country>
		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Read This Immediately - REAL SALES.</strong>

<strong>Listen - you are here because you're trying to weed out the real stuff from the junk.</strong>

<strong>Top salesperson earned $153,223 last year</strong>

Here is the deal:

We are looking for an aggressive CLOSER who can sell by phone.

And this isn’t some dead-end grind like selling mortgages, stocks, fire alarms, or any of that tired old garbage.

You’ll be working for a 20 year old consulting firm that sells and provides its services to pre-screened companies. The best part is these companies ALREADY WANT WHAT YOU’RE SELLING and they have money.
Like the title of this ad says, this is a real job with a real company.

So you are not going to get pitched some bogus pyramid scheme or anything weird. You will be working by phone representing a Norfolk, VA solid company that is 20 years old.

We are well capitalized, have an outstanding product, and an unbeatable sales process. Plus we’re selling something that people already want.

If you are selected, you will be personally trained and groomed for success by an experienced sales manager.

You will learn sales and marketing skills that will far exceed anything you’ve ever seen before, and more importantly ...you’ll have an opportunity to make an exceptional income by providing a service that genuinely helps people.

In other words, this is a job you can (and will) be very proud of.
The potential to make $150,000 a year is very real.

In fact, it’s not even that difficult to do. Here’s why.
First of all, you’re providing equipment and service to an industry that needs what you have. If they don’t currently do business with us they have at least heard of us.

Plus, you’re selling a product that people already want.

You also get paid residual income.

Our salespeople make $100,000-$150,000 a year based on a generous commission structure.

But on top of all that, you can also earn passive residual income to the tune of thousands per month.

And listen, this is NOT insurance, bank card processing, securities, or anything even remotely like that.

It’s in the consulting business and you’re selling something reliable with a long track record.

You do NOT need experience.

The founders of this company started from where you are and built a solid 20 year old company.

They started with NOTHING and are keenly aware that the secret to success is more about a good work ethic, loyalty, and DRIVE ...and NOT about degrees and “know it alls”.

If you’re selected, you’ll be trained personally by an experienced sales manager.

You will emerge with a skill set that is far more valuable than any degree or “industry experience” that you can imagine.

And you will have the opportunity to immediately start making more money than many doctors and lawyers.

Send your resume to salesopenings@outlook.com
We will respond back asking you to complete a survey to help us learn a little bit about you.

From there, you’ll learn more about the company and you’ll schedule an interview.

If you’re selected for the position, expect to start training right away.]]></description>
		<jobtype><![CDATA[Part Time]]></jobtype>
	</job>
	<job>
		<title><![CDATA[פרויקט התנדבות קיץ]]></title>
		<company><![CDATA[avis]]></company>
		<date><![CDATA[17-07-15]]></date>
		<referencenumber><![CDATA[169]]></referencenumber>
		<url><![CDATA[http://saleshiringsystems.com/job/avis-2-%d7%a4%d7%a8%d7%95%d7%99%d7%a7%d7%98-%d7%94%d7%aa%d7%a0%d7%93%d7%91%d7%95%d7%aa-%d7%a7%d7%99%d7%a5/]]></url>
		<country><![CDATA[Tel Aviv-Yafo, Israel]]></country>
		<description><![CDATA[התנדבות לחודשי הקיץ- בלוד.

ביקור בית לקשישים.]]></description>
		<jobtype><![CDATA[Full Time]]></jobtype>
	</job>
</source>